

PROJECTS

GROOVESHARK CHAT

Oct 2014 - Dec 2014

INTERACTION DESIGNER

Real client based class project to integrate a chat feature into Grooveshark's current Interface. Design process involved user research, brainstorming, wireframing, and creating an interactive prototype. Final design solution was exhibited to Grooveshark development team and Computer Science department faculty and students.

MUNCHER *Mar 2014 – Dec 2014*

DEVELOPER + DESIGNER + ARTIST

Self-initiated project created for the purpose of learning how to create mobile games for Android devices. Developed with the Cocos2d-x framework.

PAPERCUTS *Jan 2013 – Apr 2013*

TECHNICAL LEAD + LEVEL DESIGNER

Semester-long group project to familiarize students with the game design process. The game is 2D/3D Platformer developed with the Unity Engine. Final product was exhibited to faculty and students of the Computer Science department.

SUPER SLIME BLOB

Jan 2010 – Aug 2010

DEVELOPER + DESIGNER + ARTIST

Exhibition project that started in high school and continued development past graduation. The game is a 2D Platformer created with the Microsoft XNA Game Studio.

EXPERIENCE

DEVELOPER INTERNAT BIG PICTURE GAMES

Jun 2013 – Aug 2013 Gainesville, FL

Worked with the Unity Engine on a game called Flaming Narwhal. Contributions to development include updating HUD and menu screens, and reorganizing structure of existing code.

TEACHING ASSISTANT

Jan 2013 – Present Gainesville, FL

DEPARTMENT OF COMPUTER SCIENCE

Courses: Programming Fundamentals 1, Interactive Modeling and Animation Assisted three different professors with the following tasks: grading, leading weekly discussion sections, holding office hours, advising students, lecture planning, and generating guiz and examination questions.

JONATHAN LUCKA

DDRESS STREET NAME

APARTMENT NO. CITY. STATE ZIP

PHONE (***)*** ****

EMAIL JOZZLEO6@GMAIL.COM WEB JLUCKA625.GITHUB.IO

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science in Digital Arts and Sciences University of Florida August 2010 – May 2015

AWARDS

Top 100 out of 5000 Spotify Code Quest Feburary 2012

SKILLSET

Game Design
UI Design
Interaction Design
3D Modeling
Graphic Design
Web Design
Computer Graphics

TOOLSET

Unity Engine
Autodesk Maya
Adobe Photoshop
Adobe Illustrator
Processing
Java
C/C++
HTML/CSS
Javascript/jQuery
Git
Balsamiq
InVision

Microsoft Office